<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <channel>
        <title>Pages on Brass Wrench&#39;s Library</title>
        <link>https://www.brasswrench.com/en/page/</link>
        <description>Recent content in Pages on Brass Wrench&#39;s Library</description>
        <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
        <language>en</language>
        <copyright>BrassWrench</copyright>
        <lastBuildDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2024 20:29:20 +0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.brasswrench.com/en/page/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" /><item>
        <title>About</title>
        <link>https://www.brasswrench.com/en/about/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 Nov 2024 22:44:11 +0800</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://www.brasswrench.com/en/about/</guid>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;  Welcome to the Brass Wrench&amp;rsquo;s Library! I’m a junior AI major student from the Harbin Institute of Technology’s Harbin campus, and &amp;ldquo;Brass Wrench&amp;rdquo; is my pseudonym—inspired by the revolutionary Minecraft mod &amp;ldquo;Create&amp;rdquo;. This is my personal knowledge repository, a place where I record and organize knowledge spanning various fundamental concepts, technical principles, and solutions encountered in my learning and research.&lt;br&gt;
  I have a deep interest in many fields, though often with fleeting enthusiasm. Nonetheless, this tendency has enabled me to gather a wide array of knowledge across many disciplines, including basic sciences, computer science, engineering, economics, medicine, law, sociology, philosophy, and even the arts. In the near future, I plan to systematically organize and publish this knowledge across the pages of this library. These pages are interconnected by rigorous context and logical links and are written according to the strict teaching standards of each discipline, allowing visitors to easily learn, understand, and search for content. This knowledge repository will not be limited to theoretical information; it will also include practical experiences and solutions I’ve developed. I aim to make my writing as self-contained as possible, minimizing external references, avoiding conclusions without proper explanations, and ensuring that every point is logically consistent. This way, every visitor can build a solid foundation for their studies and research within this library.&lt;br&gt;
  But unfortunately, I am a patient with bipolar order. My memory is really poor due to recurrent seizures and long-term psychiatric medication, which inspired me to create this library as a way to effectively manage and reinforce the knowledge I’ve acquired. In a sense, this is my &amp;ldquo;second brain&amp;rdquo;. I hope that one day, when I suddenly need a specific piece of information, I can quickly locate it here. This library will help me systematically review and organize my learning materials, thereby improving my efficiency and research capabilities.&lt;br&gt;
  Moreover, I hope this library will be a valuable resource for others with similar needs. In this era of information overload, many people are searching for useful resources. My library is designed to be a centralized, comprehensive knowledge base that can help visitors swiftly find the information they need, serving as a valuable reference to foster the spread and sharing of knowledge. I hope you find useful content here, and I welcome any suggestions or feedback to help me improve and expand this knowledge repository.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;  Here is how to use the library.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;  The Brass Wrench&amp;rsquo;s Library organizes a wealth of resources across disciplines, including basic sciences, computer science, engineering, economics, medicine, law, sociology, philosophy, and the arts. Content is hierarchically categorized by subject area. Visitors can use the side navigation bar to click on “Categories” and browse content related to a specific field. Additionally, the search bar in the side navigation bar provides the function of keyword search for all articles, and the search box in the upper right corner provides the function of searching for the keywords of the current page. Different fields are presented in the form of medium-to-long articles organized by thematic categories and identification numbers. Notably, internal links enable readers to jump to related content within pages and across sections, ensuring logical coherence for comprehensive cross-disciplinary inquiry. After clicking on a link, you can return to your previous position by using the arrow button on the right.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;  Please note that this library is still in its early stages, and much of the content is not yet complete. Your patience is appreciated. I sincerely hope you have an enjoyable learning experience here! And I welcome any feedback on how I can improve!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Reward</title>
        <link>https://www.brasswrench.com/en/reward/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 Nov 2024 22:42:25 +0800</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://www.brasswrench.com/en/reward/</guid>
        <description>&lt;div style=&#34;display: flex; justify-content: center; align-items: Center;&#34;&gt;
    &lt;div&gt;
        &lt;img src=&#34;https://www.brasswrench.com/reward/figures/wechat_reward.png&#34; width=&#34;100%&#34;&gt;
        &lt;p style=&#34;text-align:center; margin-top: 0; margin-bottom:0&#34;&gt;pay by Wechat&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div&gt;
        &lt;img src=&#34;https://www.brasswrench.com/reward/figures/alipay_reward.png&#34; width=&#34;100%&#34;&gt;
        &lt;p style=&#34;text-align:center; margin-top: 0; margin-bottom:0&#34;&gt;pay by Alipay&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;‌&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Draft</title>
        <link>https://www.brasswrench.com/en/draft/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 Nov 2024 22:41:13 +0800</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://www.brasswrench.com/en/draft/</guid>
        <description></description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Archive</title>
        <link>https://www.brasswrench.com/en/archives/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 Nov 2024 22:40:38 +0800</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://www.brasswrench.com/en/archives/</guid>
        <description></description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Tags</title>
        <link>https://www.brasswrench.com/en/tagcloud/</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 14 Sep 2024 17:20:54 +0800</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://www.brasswrench.com/en/tagcloud/</guid>
        <description></description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Links</title>
        <link>https://www.brasswrench.com/en/link/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://www.brasswrench.com/en/link/</guid>
        <description></description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Messsage</title>
        <link>https://www.brasswrench.com/en/message/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://www.brasswrench.com/en/message/</guid>
        <description></description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Search</title>
        <link>https://www.brasswrench.com/en/search/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://www.brasswrench.com/en/search/</guid>
        <description></description>
        </item>
        
    </channel>
</rss>
