<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <channel>
        <title>Pages on Brass Wrench&#39;s Library</title>
        <link>https://www.brasswrench.cn/en/page/</link>
        <description>Recent content in Pages on Brass Wrench&#39;s Library</description>
        <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
        <language>en</language>
        <copyright>Brass Wrench</copyright>
        <lastBuildDate>Sat, 21 Sep 2024 07:40:14 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.brasswrench.cn/en/page/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" /><item>
        <title>Tags</title>
        <link>https://www.brasswrench.cn/en/tagcloud/</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 14 Sep 2024 17:20:54 +0800</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://www.brasswrench.cn/en/tagcloud/</guid>
        <description></description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Archives</title>
        <link>https://www.brasswrench.cn/en/archives/</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 14 Sep 2024 17:20:50 +0800</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://www.brasswrench.cn/en/archives/</guid>
        <description></description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>About</title>
        <link>https://www.brasswrench.cn/en/about/</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 14 Sep 2024 15:08:43 +0800</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://www.brasswrench.cn/en/about/</guid>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;  Welcome to Brass Wrench&amp;rsquo;s Personal Library! I am a junior AI student at Harbin Institute of Technology, and &amp;ldquo;Brass Wrench&amp;rdquo; is my alias, inspired by the revolutionary Minecraft mod &amp;ldquo;Create&amp;rdquo; where the brass wrench is an iconic tool. This is my personal knowledge repository, where I record and organize the foundational concepts, technical principles, and solutions I encounter throughout my studies and research.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;  I have a keen interest in many fields, although I often dive into them only for short bursts of enthusiasm. This, however, has allowed me to accumulate a broad range of knowledge across various disciplines, including mathematics, physics, computer science, artificial intelligence, automation, mechanical engineering, and electrical and electronic engineering. This knowledge repository is not limited to theoretical knowledge but also includes practical experiences and solutions I&amp;rsquo;ve developed in certain areas. Due to my poor memory, the primary purpose of creating this blog is to find an effective way to manage and consolidate the knowledge I learn, aiming to serve as my &amp;ldquo;second brain.&amp;rdquo; In the future, I hope that whenever a specific idea or concept comes to mind, I can quickly locate the information I need. This library will help me systematically organize and review my learning content, ultimately improving my learning efficiency and research capabilities.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;  Additionally, I hope to publicly share my work through this blog so that those with similar needs can easily find the knowledge they are seeking. In this era of information overload, I believe many people are searching for useful resources. My library aims to provide a centralized knowledge base to help visitors quickly find the information they need, while also serving as a valuable reference to promote the dissemination and sharing of knowledge. I hope you find the content here useful, and I welcome any suggestions and feedback to further improve and develop this knowledge repository together.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Link</title>
        <link>https://www.brasswrench.cn/en/link/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://www.brasswrench.cn/en/link/</guid>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Here are some friend links.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Message</title>
        <link>https://www.brasswrench.cn/en/message/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://www.brasswrench.cn/en/message/</guid>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Easy Comment!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Search</title>
        <link>https://www.brasswrench.cn/en/search/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://www.brasswrench.cn/en/search/</guid>
        <description></description>
        </item>
        
    </channel>
</rss>
